{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Find the maximum value of $25y + x^{2}y$ of $x$ and $y$ add up to 10 and both are greater than zero.",
      "question_choice": [
        "$250$",
        "$260$",
        "$270$",
        "$280$"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A piece of string is 480cm. It is cut into two pieces and a square made with one piece and a rectanglel twice as wide as high made with the other. Find the minimum of the sum of the square's area and rectangle's area.",
      "question_choice": [
        "$1256cm^{2}$",
        "$1004cm^{2}$",
        "$6776cm^{2}$",
        "$7251cm^{2}$"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "A parabola has a turning point at $(4.5, 6)$ and a $y$ intercept of $18$. What is its equation?",
      "question_choice": [
        "$y = 0.586x^{2} + 61x + 9$",
        "$y = 0.526x^{2} + 12.3x + 12$",
        "$y = 0.412x^{2} + 18x + 11.1$",
        "$y = 0.5926x^{2} - 5.3333x + 18$"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A parabola's tangent is parallel with the x=axis at $x = 2$ and is at $45\\degree$ to the x-axis at x = 3. What is its tangent's gradient at $x = 8$?",
      "question_choice": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "6",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The function $f(x) = 2x^{3} + kx^{2} + 5$ has a minimum turning point when $x = 1$ What are the co-ordinates of the maximum turning point?",
      "question_choice": [
        "$(0, 5)$",
        "$(1, 7)$",
        "$(2, 5)$",
        "$(2. 4)$"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "The movement of an object is recorded from the time it passes a fixed point. After $t$ seconds it has a speed $vms^{-1}$ which can be modelled by the function $v(t) = 0.5t^{2} - 2t + 1$ Use calculus to find how long it takes to reach an acceleration of $2.8ms^{-2}$",
      "question_choice": [
        "$t = 4.6s$",
        "$t = 4.8s$",
        "$t = 5.0s$",
        "$t = 5.2s$"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The line $y = ax + b$ is a tangent to the graph of the function $y = 2x^{2} - 3x + 1$ at the point $(2, 3)$. Find the values of $a$ and $b$",
      "question_choice": [
        "$a = 5$ $y = 5x + 7$",
        "$a = 5$ $y = 5x - 7$",
        "$a = 7$ $y = 5x + 7$",
        "$a = 7$ $y = 5x - 7$"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The gradient graph of a function $f(x)$ is given by $f'(x) = 6x^{2} - 2x + 4$ The point $(1, 3)$ lies on the graph. Find the equation of the function $f(x)$",
      "question_choice": [
        "$f(x) = 2x^{3} - x^{2} + 4x - 2$",
        "$f(x) = 2x^{3} - 3x^{2} + 1x - 3$",
        "$f(x) = 2x^{3} - 2x^{2} + 4x - 5$",
        "$f(x) = 2x^{3} - x^{2} + 4x - 8$"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "A chemical is slowly leaking onto the floor. The chemical spreads out from the point where it lands in a shape that can be modelled by a circle of the radius $rcm$. At a time $t$ seconds after the chemical leak is noticed, $r$ is given by $0.1t + 2$. Use calculus to find the rate of change of area of the circle, with respect to time, when its radius is $10cm$",
      "question_choice": [
        "$3\\pi cm^{2}s^{-1}$",
        "$4\\pi cm^{2}s^{-1}$",
        "$\\pi cm^{2}s^{-1}$",
        "$2\\pi cm^{2}s^{-1}$"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    }
  ,
    {
      "question": "Find the equation of the tangent to the curve $f(x) = x^{3} - 2x^{2} + x$ at the point(2, 2) on the curve.",
      "question_choice": [
        "$y = 3x + 4$",
        "$y = 5x - 8$",
        "$y = 5x + 4$",
        "$y = 3x - 7$"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}